You...
I finally found you, Lycanthrope.
So it is you.
You're the one looking for me.
If you already know,
that makes things simple.
You'll pay for what you
did to our brothers!
Najak!
I wouldn't recommend trying to fight me.
Many of your friends are still
trapped at the moon altar.
Don't you care what happens to them?
Tell us one thing. What do you want?
To become this nation's—no,
this world's king.
And to do that, I need your blood.
Come with me.
Don't worry.
When I become king, I'll allow you
werewolves to serve me alongside vampires.
Screw you!
I'll go with you.
In exchange, promise you
won't hurt my brothers.
Very well.
Okay. I'll do as you say.
Khan!
Don't do it!
You still can't—
I'll be fine.
Take care of Najak.
Shall we go?
Someone you've been wanting
to see is there, too.
- Dark Moon: The Blood Altar -
- Vargr's Blood -
Shion, are you okay?
I'm fine.
Sooha will heal us again, right?
Actually, I think our
healing is slowing down.
My grip feels weak.
So does mine.
Did something happen to Sooha?
Let's hurry.
Something's coming.
What are you doing here?
Dardan took Khan?!
We're running out of time.
Once the full moon rises...
He'll take her power.
Do we not stand a chance?
I'm not letting that happen!
Either way, I can't believe
Sooha is a princess.
Sooha!
She gave them too much power.
Her name is Princess Selen.
Haven't you missed her?
Princess Selen?
Oh, right. You don't know.
In that case, I'll enlighten you.
She's the reincarnation of
an ancient kingdom's princess?
You must've noticed it, too.
Sooha has the power to control us.
Please, guys!
We also instinctively want to protect her.
You're right.
So, were you guys reincarnated like her?
No, in our case...
Princess Selen used her dying breath
to send our souls centuries
into the future and save us.
We'd forgotten for hundreds of years and
hid that we were vampires until now.
We didn't even know why we existed.
But the princess was reborn as Sooha.
Meeting her brought back
our past memories.
Of everything that happened
when the kingdom fell.
And that we exist to protect Sooha.
The time has come to settle
matters with Dardan.
This time, we'll stop him.
Yeah.
Sooha...
Now, give me your blood.
Give it to me, or else...
I'm worried.
Khan still hasn't transformed
into a wolf a single time.
This is the power of Vargr's blood.
Sooha! Are you okay?
Wake up!
Who said you could
lay hands on the princess?
You bastard! What did you do to Sooha?!
I told you, your brothers' lives
depend on your cooperation.
As a Lycanthrope, you won't sit
back and watch your brothers die.
Am I wrong?
Get away from the princess.
Didn't you hear me?!
You've also fallen for her,
haven't you?
Then you should be willing to
sacrifice your brothers to save her!
You can't save either
because you can't choose!
The sun...
- Dark Moon: The Blood Altar -
Now I have everything I need.
The incantation.
The princess.
The blood of Vargr.
When the full moon rises high in the
night sky, I will recite the incantation.
The power sealed within the altar will be
released and passed on to the princess.
Then I will claim that power for myself.
If only I were stronger...
Lycanthrope.
That voice...
Within your veins courses my blood.
The blood of Vargr, the wolf god.
To our kind, you are like the moon.
You can awaken their strength.
But how?
Your instincts will show you the way.
Call out to the others
and become our moon.
Use your power to protect
the princess you serve.
I carry Vargr's blood.
That's a Lycanthrope!
It's a Lycanthrope!
He's here to save us!
Run, guys!
Hurry!
You're wasting your time!
You told me not to touch
the princess, right?
Well, right back at you!
I won't let you have your way!
Silence!
You're just a werewolf.
You think you can beat me now?
If you defy me, I'll kill you.
You and your brothers.
What's that?
Sounds like a lot of them.
They're not enemies.
They're our kind.
What happened? Where did you come from?
The moon altar.
Where's Khan?
Is he all right?
Khan? You mean that Lycanthrope?
He saved us.
Then Khan...
...transformed into a wolf!
So, where's Khan?
He's facing Dardan all by himself.
Stay there.
The seal has begun to release.
This is the power passed down for
generations in the ancient kingdom.
I can feel its tremendous energy
just by standing near it.
Such overwhelming power!
And this will all be mine.
Princess.
Let's begin.
Look!
That light... Is that...
The royal power sealed in the altar...
The ritual must've started.
Let's go!
This power will be all mine.
I won't let you have it.
Stop!
You mutt!
I can't allow you to live any longer!
Let's go!
Khan, are you okay?!
Heli...
You're too late.
Why did you even bother coming?
Sooha.
Her hair color... Could it be...
Khan!
He's badly injured.
Hang in there!
I'm fine.
How are our brothers?
They're all safe.
I... I see.
Is it because she granted us power?
No, this is...
Our power...
It's being drained from our bodies.
The power Sooha shared with
us is returning to her.
This is bad!
We have to stop him, now!
Jakah, I'm going to draw
Dardan's attention.
While he's distracted, save Sooha.
My telepathy's not working.
Jakah, get Sooha!
I can't use my power?!
This is the best part.
You mustn't interfere
with Lord Dardan's plans!
Watch as everything becomes mine.
Both this power and
the princess belong to me.
Sear this sight into your eyes!
Let's go, guys!
Yeah!
Let us handle this!
Go defeat Dardan!
Dardan!
You don't stand a chance against me.
How laughable.
You were once the kingdom's
greatest knights.
And now you're kneeling at my feet.
Soon, you'll lose all your power.
Once you lose the power you were granted,
you'll realize you're nothing at all.
Next time, Episode 12:
"Dark Moon: The Moon Altar."
- The Moon Altar -